- Tonight,
on "The Bachelorette"...
- Whoo!
[bicycle bell ringing]
- We are in the Netherlands...
- You're the best captain
I've had in a long time.
- [laughing]
And I'm falling
for multiple guys.
- I'm crazy about you.
both: Whoo!
- I'm 100% feeling Hannah.
I want this so bad...
- I have
no doubt in my mind
that I can be the guy
getting on one knee for you.
- I'm sure it's written all
over my dang face right now.
I love you.
- How could I not
be more confident?
She's falling in love
with me for sure.
[laughs]
It's like I know.
- You gave me your word.
Your "stay in your lane."
Like, it just,
like, doesn't end.
- He's gone, so guess what.
One less of us.
It's simple math.
- You're right, now there's
five guys who can't stand you.
- He does such a good job
of manipulating.
- You are a weasel.
It's a game to Luke.
That's all it is.
And the bad guy's going home.
- I don't care
what you said to her.
I've been nothing
but truthful with Hannah,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
- [crying] This is by far
the hardest good-bye
I've had to say,
and I don't know what to do,
and I'm scared.
[dramatic musical sting]
- It all starts right now.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- This week,
we are in the Netherlands.
This is the last week
before hometowns,
and it feels really good
to be moving past
all the drama.
I just wanna continue
on the feelings
that I'm having for these men
and make sure
that I feel confident
going into next week
at the hometowns.
I'm obviously very excited
to get to explore Amsterdam
with seven awesome men.
[folksy music]
♪ ♪
[boat horn blares]
- Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
Wow.
- I don't know
what is gonna be
at the end of this for me.
I'm falling
for multiple people
in totally different ways,
and so that's really exciting,
but scary.
- This is beautiful.
- Wow!
- I feel like I've held back
a lot in this experience,
so it's important to me
to open up to these men.
And that's what
this week's about.
- It's a big week, man.
I mean, you should be,
like motivated
for her to meet your family.
- It's a big deal.
- Having had the earliest
one-on-one of the guys
that are still here,
there are a lot of questions
I have,
and I'm sure, like, she wants
to get to know me better.
Especially going
into next week.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey!
- Hello.
- Hey, y'all.
- Hey.
- Hey, there she is.
- You okay?
You sound like you're getting
a little sick.
- I'm great, guys.
I'm great.
What's going on?
- Just enjoying Amsterdam.
- I am so excited to be here.
Bringing y'all here
is a really big deal for me.
This is a really big week.
Next week is hometowns,
and I'm going back home
with four guys.
And it's really important
for me
that not only
I feel comfortable,
but that you guys
feel comfortable knowing
who I am.
I'm excited about the dates
that we have.
It's going to be
a picturesque setting
to really just fall in love.
And, you know,
speaking of dates,
let's start one now.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Nice.
- Oh, boy.
- So, Jed, you wanna go
on a date with me today?
- Yes!
- [laughs]
- There you go.
- Well, y'all...y'all
are the best,
but I've gotta go explore
the city.
- Have my lady home
by 9:00 now.
- Hey.
Ooh!
Here, let's go this way.
- Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
- He didn't bring his guitar,
did he?
- I hope not.
- You know, you just got
to look at any time
as quality time.
You can take advantage
of any time that you have.
- I know, myself, I'm gonna
do everything I can
to make sure time isn't robbed
from myself and you guys.
- Most importantly,
robbed from Hannah.
- Exactly.
Yeah, she needs this.
- It's easy for you to say
she needs this,
but you're the one--
the culprit behind it.
Every time,
you're the common denominator.
- That's a fact.
- Yeah.
- So I just--let's nip it
in the bud this week, maybe.
[train bell rings]
- This is so cool.
- I know.
- Let's get some chocolates.
Oh, my God!
You have some...
- There's so many options.
- Really good chocolates.
We get all of them.
- We do?
- I'm so excited to hang
out with Jed today.
- Hannah, will you accept
this pansy?
- I will.
Jed is up for everything,
excited about everything.
- We would end up
in this store, Hannah.
- I think Jed and I are
pretty natural together,
but I just wanna make sure
that continues.
Welcome to my boat.
I'm your captain.
- You're driving?
- Yeah.
- Oh, [bleep].
- Last week, he told me
he was falling for me
and put the romance level
up here with our relationship.
So I just wanna feel
secure today
in my feelings for him,
and I've gotta be open.
- You're the best captain
I've had in a long time.
- [laughs]
[bright music]
- Oh.
- Oh!
I saw this going down
the street earlier.
- I know!
I did too.
- Is there a dance to this?
♪ ♪
Let's heel click.
One, two, three.
- Oh, shoot!
Wait, do it again.
Do it again!
- Ready?
One, two, three.
- I can't do it in these.
Can't do it in these jeans.
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Oh, hi, hi.
- How are you?
- Okay.
- No.
- No?
So you are...
- English.
- English?
- Yeah, yeah.
- American.
- Okay, okay.
- We're not English.
- What are you doing
in Amsterdam?
- We're on a date.
- Date?
- Yeah.
- And how long do you know
each other?
- Long enough to know things.
- Yeah?
Long enough to know things?
- To make a decision.
- To make decisions, yeah.
- Yeah?
- Y'all been together
a long time?
- Yeah, we have been together
for 54 years.
- Wow.
- Oh, my gosh, congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- But we spent together
before we decided to marry
only ten days.
- What?
- Yeah.
- When was the moment you knew?
- I don't know.
I think it was written
in the stars.
- Amazing.
You're gonna make me cry.
- [laughs]
- No, no, no, no, no,
don't do that.
- Here's to making the most
of each and every moment
and seeing if our love
is also written in the stars.
- Aww.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
[sentimental music]
♪ ♪
These feelings have been
so easy.
That's what's just blowing
my mind.
It's just, like,
constantly growing
and it's just very, like,
effortless feelings.
- Yeah.
I, um...
I kinda feel the same way.
It's hard for me to, like...
I want you to know I take
a little while to say stuff,
especially in this.
But, like, I'm really
just, like, protective
of my heart
and the person that I'm gonna
spend the rest of my life with
and...
- Yeah.
- And I wanna say...
- What you mean.
- Just a lot harder
than I thought,
because it's, like,
my feelings are growing so much
with you and then I go
to another conversation,
and I have to be, like, all in.
And it's, like...
- It's hard.
- And then I'm like,
"Oh, my God, Jed," like...
- This is all growing so much
for both of us,
and I think that it would
make you actually probably
feel better in a way
if you just open up.
- I know.
I'm trying.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
It's always been hard for me
to articulate my feelings,
and I'm trying to open
my heart more.
But I just don't know
what to say
to these guys that I really
have feelings for,
because, like, I don't know
how much is too much.
I don't know, like, exactly
how I feel.
I don't know.
I've just had
a really good time.
- I know, we've already made,
like, some really cool,
amazing memories.
- I know I'm supposed to trust
and not be afraid,
and I'm gonna really try
to take that into tonight.
It's just hard.
But I really want to,
'cause Jed is worth
me trying for.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[bell rings]
- What is that?
- Date card, huh?
- This week is
really important.
I had such an early
one-on-one date
that didn't go to plan,
because you know, she was sick.
I really do need
that one-on-one date
to get to know her better
and kind of develop
that level of comfort
before, you know,
having Hannah meet my family.
- All righty.
♪ ♪
"Tyler, will you ride
into the sunset with me?
Hannah."
- Hell yeah, I will.
Yeah!
- Man.
- Lucky guy.
- There you go, baby.
- Congrats.
- Nice.
- I'm stoked.
I'm stoked, man, I'm happy.
- I would have loved
to be on this one-on-one date.
Obviously,
I think we all would have,
but there's another
one-on-one date this week.
So, like, just kind of holding
on to the hope
that I'll be on that one.
Think that's all you can do.
- Definitely.
[tram bell dings]
[romantic music]
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Are you wearing...
what color is that?
- [laughing] I don't know.
- Hi.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- Hi.
- [gasps]
Aww.
Tulips.
Today was really good
for Jed and I,
because, I don't know,
it just felt like
it was like our date.
We were
boyfriend and girlfriend
exploring Amsterdam together.
We're going in here.
- This place looks lovely.
[gasps]
Ooh.
- Last week, he told me
he was falling in love
with me.
And I've been
really hesitant about letting
anybody know where I'm at
in my feelings,
but today made me realize
where my feelings really were.
So tonight I feel like
I wanna open up
and show how I'm feeling
about him.
- It was--today was...
one of the best
dates I've ever had.
- There were just so many,
like, sweet moments too.
- I know.
I know.
- I started this whole thing,
like, wanting y'all
to be real and raw and, like,
needing you to be that,
and then I realized that
sometimes I'm not always that.
I am, but to an extent,
you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- So I'm just, like,
going to try
to be as open as I can.
[exhales]
I have feelings
for multiple people here,
and I don't know what to do.
And so I feel like
you have noticed
that I'm, like, holding back.
And I'm holding back
with everyone and everything,
because, like, I don't want
to hurt anybody.
I got hurt, so I'm just,
like, stuck,
because I don't want
to, like, go there.
Even if I feel that way,
I don't wanna go there,
so I'm just, like, holding it,
because, like,
there's just so much going on.
I have so much to handle.
- You have, like, a lot
on your plate.
I get it.
But, like,
I see the other relationships
and then what we have going
and then the drama.
And I can see
how it stacks on you,
and I don't want it
to just be on you.
I wanna take some.
And whatever I have to do,
if I have to hear about things
that I don't like,
that's just how it goes
in relationships sometimes.
You have to hear things
that don't make you happy,
but you do it
because you love that person.
And I wanna do that.
I wanna build a foundationally
powerful relationship,
and I want you to feel
like you can open up.
- There was this moment
today...
we were dancing,
and you know how you,
like, clicked your heels up?
- Mm-hmm.
- And then, like,
I clicked my heels up
and I [bleep] it up
the first time.
And then I was like,
"Let's do it again,"
and then, like, we did it.
I don't know.
It was in that moment
I was like,
I remember I was, like,
laughing.
And it was like everything
around me was, like, spinning
and I just saw your face.
And you kissed me.
And it was in that moment
that I was, like,
"Oh, my gosh, this is real."
I don't know why the click
of the heels...
- [chuckles]
- And that kiss
in front of that organ,
like, made me finally, like,
be confident
and feel safe to say, like...
[exhales deeply]
Jed...
I'm falling in love with you.
And I'm shaking inside,
because I think I've known it
for a little while,
but I haven't said it at all.
And I don't know,
it feels really good,
but it feels also, like,
really scary,
because I don't know
what the end of this is for me.
I don't know what the end is,
but I know that right now
it feels really good.
- My heart just fell through
the earth.
It'll be back later, but wow.
Um...
- It feels really good to say.
- Let me have my moment.
Just let me have my moment.
[laughs]
All right.
All right, I'm good.
Um...
- [laughs]
Yay!
- I feel the same way,
and I'm--yeah,
I'm falling in love with you.
- [squeals]
Ooh.
- I'm not gonna be able
to sleep for three days.
- Maybe I can help you sleep.
[cheerful music]
- [gasps]
- Jed, thank you
for trusting me
at the beginning
of this thing.
And when you opened your heart,
you allowed me to feel
secure and safe.
And...I'm so excited
to meet your family
and find out
what makes Jed Jed.
So Jed...
Will you accept this rose?
- Since I've had the best day,
yes.
- [laughs]
What if you had a bad day?
- Please.
- Would you still accept it?
- I just--I've had
the best day.
I can't even, like,
think about a bad day.
♪ ♪
Today was the best day ever,
and I'm so excited.
We're going to Tennessee.
She's gonna get to meet
the Wyatt family,
and they're gonna love
this girl.
I know.
And it's just getting
more and more real.
- It really is beautiful.
But I like looking at this.
- I like to look at this.
[soft piano music]
- I feel like since
I've, like, said everything
I need to say to Jed,
I'm, like...
[sighs]
Free to feel
and to move forward
and to see the future.
[laughs]
I could see a life with Jed
after this.
Like, a good life with Jed.
There's a bunch of signs
pointing to it
being written in the stars.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Hello. Whatcha got?
- Pickled herring is one of
my worst nightmares.
Ready?
- Oh, my gosh.
It's actually not that bad.
- This is not gonna go good.
[coughs]
- You need to man up.
- [coughs]
- And then...
- Your time's coming
to an end.
- Excuse me?
I wish you were a fly
on the wall
and you could see
their character be exposed.
- I got thrown under the bus
but I'm gonna do something
about it.
- I've been nothing
but truthful with Hannah,
and you are not gonna
mess it up!
[dramatic musical sting]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Last night with Jed,
I told him
I was
falling in love with him,
so that kind of set the bar
for me in this
very, very high.
Today, I have a one-on-one
with Tyler,
and I'm so excited to see him.
So far in this journey,
I've been really hesitant
about, like,
letting anybody know
where I'm at in my feelings
with each of the relationships.
And I think this week
it's time for me
to start opening up
for me to feel confident
in meeting their families.
Hey.
- What's up?
- Hey, good lookin'.
- How are you, gorgeous?
- I'm good.
Whoo!
- What's up?
Looking beautiful.
- Today we are going to explore
The Hague,
and it's gonna be really fun.
- Let's do it.
Top of the world right now.
Our last one-on-one was
one of the best nights
I've ever had.
That's what makes me
so excited about today,
just is how much we grew
in that one-on-one
and from where we are now
to what we can grow to today.
If I get a rose,
I'm bringing her to Mama.
I would love for Hannah to meet
Nana and Mama
and all--the whole crew.
I mean, everything we've done
together has been so easy
and so much fun and flowed
and...
that I don't think--I have
no worries about today at all.
- So, we're not just walking
around The Hague.
We're horsing around The Hague.
[both laugh]
Have you been
horseback riding before?
- When I was, like,
a little kid,
I had horseback riding party
at my house.
- How'd it go?
- It was good,
but I'm a little nervous
around these things now.
- You're nervous?
Don't--can't be nervous.
- I'm not gonna be nervous.
- 'Cause they can pick up
on nervous energy.
- I got it.
I'm good, I'm good.
- Here's all the good energy.
- Ooh, that felt good, girl.
- Did that feel good?
So now you got all
the good energy.
- I'm not gonna lie--I'm a
little freaked out by horses.
They're a big ol' thing.
Throw that thing in there.
- Oh, wow, this is really high.
- Ready?
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Ooh!
- Told you I got you.
I'm trying to act cool,
like I got no fear,
but I was definitely nervous
getting up on there.
And I hope she knows I'll
pretty do anything for her.
Whoa, whoa!
- What are you doing?
- [clicks tongue]
- No--
Now you're making mine scared.
Come on, little horsey.
Let's go in a circle.
- Forward.
[clicks tongue]
- Now let's go.
Go.
- Follow me.
I got you.
- Go.
I can't get it to go.
- No, nope.
Nope, nope.
There we go.
- Oh my gosh, look at us.
Ooh.
[gasps]
Have you had these waffles?
- No.
Oh.
- Go.
- Come on.
Go.
- There we go.
[smooching noise]
- What are you doing?
Hey.
- [laughs]
- All right.
He doesn't want the waffles.
[gasps] I love ice cream!
- Come on.
- Mr. Ice Cream Man.
- Can we get some ice cream?
- Uh-uh.
You, Nellie.
What did we talk about?
We talked about listening
to your mother.
- How much do I owe you?
- Three euro.
- Three euros?
Here's two.
- You better stop now.
Stop.
This is a disaster!
- Come on.
I'm trying to come to you.
I got something for you.
- Oh, you got me treats.
[laughing] Oh, no,
you're going the wrong way.
- Hello.
What you got?
- [speaking Dutch]
- Ew.
- Yeah, she'd love that.
Pickled herring is, like,
one of my worst nightmares.
Come here.
- Ew, God.
- Come here.
- You have to feed me this?
- I'm about to feed you.
You ready?
- Oh, my gosh.
[quirky music]
♪ ♪
- How is it?
- It's actually not that bad.
- She eats it.
She crushes it,
and I was like,
"Oh, God, this is not
gonna go good."
♪ ♪
Mm-mm.
[gags]
- Oh--
[laughs]
- [coughing]
- [laughs]
- You have a weak stomach?
- Oh, yeah.
- Aww.
- [coughs]
- They're not good?
- No bueno.
- You need to man up.
- [groans] Ah...
Today was really fun,
but neither one of us
knew what we were doing
and we could not, like,
get it together.
- Yeah.
I needed today big time.
- You did? Why?
- Just 'cause, like,
last couple of weeks
I was getting frustrated.
- Why? Okay.
- Not with you, just, like,
I felt bad
'cause, like, stuff was going
down at that, like, house
and, like,
spilling over to you.
And like,
I was getting frustrated,
'cause that was, like,
missed opportunities.
And, like, I feel like
you need those opportunities
more than anyone does,
you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, there was times
where I would
just have to get up
and leave the room,
'cause I was--
- Missed opportunities how?
Just--I'm making you explain.
- You know, cocktail parties
not working out.
Like, you need that
more than any of us need it.
- But how are you--like,
how are you feeling
with everything going on?
- I feel--in regards to what,
me and you?
- Just--yeah, just, like,
this whole thing.
Like, I wanna know, like,
how you're struggling.
- Yeah, I mean,
there's like times
where I'll get in my head,
you know?
And I'm just like--
- How? Why?
- It's like I see you
and it's like
I go through these days
and then I, like...
it was just like...
I've never really--
I'll tell you what.
Riga was probably
my hardest time.
I don't know what it was,
but, like, getting in my head
all week.
I wasn't sleeping at all,
like, I was tripping.
- Yeah, I wanna know how.
I want more details.
I want all the details.
- All the details?
- Yeah.
I wanna know, like,
how you were getting
in your head, like, exactly.
- Mm-hmm.
It was just, like,
the first time
I, like, started comparing
myself to other people
and seeing you, like,
put everything back
in perspective
and back on track.
- What made you start
comparing?
Was it a moment?
Like, I'm just,
like--I'm trying to like--
- I don't know.
I'm trying to think.
I don't think it was
a moment.
It was just, like--just time.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- 'Cause I don't want you
to hold back,
'cause then I don't wanna
hold back.
'Cause I know I've been
struggling with that too.
But, you know, like...
if you're inviting me in,
I'll, like, accept it.
But I need to, like, feel
that you really are,
and that's why I'm, like,
pushing you right now.
- Yeah.
- Like, I wanna really know.
- We're in this thing.
- Yeah.
- And I wanna know, what--like,
what's going on in that thing.
In this thing
and in this thing.
[soft neigh, snuffling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[bicycle bell rings]
- Love it.
- It's really pretty.
- The Netherlands
will have special place
in my heart for sure.
- Mine too.
Today, I felt like
Tyler was holding back
a little bit.
And so I just need him
to really open up
about where he's at.
I hate the [bleep].
Like, I can't stand it.
I don't wanna hear
about how it's good.
I wanna know the dirty
and the raw
and the things that, like,
have scarred you.
Tonight, cheers to learning
more about each other.
- Yeah.
- Cheers.
- When you're honest
and I'm honest,
and we're, like,
able to, like, share things
with each other that are hard
and scary,
it makes you grow stronger.
- So, what a day.
- What a day.
It was beautiful day
to have a day too.
- I know.
- I was a little fearful
going up on that horse today.
- I could tell.
And I'll say, like,
of course it was fun.
Like, I always have
a great time with you,
but I just felt like
there was just something,
like, little off,
like you were nervous.
- There was a big moment
for me today.
And it was kind of, you know,
like when you, you know--
'Cause you want me
to be open.
- I was trying, man.
- I really do appreciate you
digging and digging
and pulling and pulling
with this.
I don't really open up
to anybody.
I think I've always had
a hard time with it,
'cause back at home, you know,
like, you know,
my parents, they got divorced,
you know?
So it was like,
seeing what they went through,
it was like, "Yeah, I'm not
having a relationship.
I'm not going through that,"
you know?
I've seen so much through them,
like, good and bad, you know?
You know, my dad was on top
of the world,
and, you know, we were living
in this house on the water,
which, if I go to Jupiter we'll
drive by it, and I'll show you.
He came from
absolutely nothing.
- My dad too.
- He was able to get
to that point
and have his family
on the water
and, like, live this dream
that he wasn't supposed
to have.
But the market crashed,
and he lost everything.
And we all got moved
into this small house
and just--things didn't work.
I think my parents had a hard
time turning to each other,
and they kind of turned away
from each other.
And eventually,
my pops had to move out,
and it was hard to see that,
you know,
and kind of made me stuff
things away, put things away.
And, like, my biggest fear
is to, you know,
fail at marriage.
- I can really relate.
Like, my parents
are still together,
and I love that my parents
but, like, the way
they communicate
is not the way that I wanna
communicate in a marriage.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm really taking the time
here to figure out
"What do I want?"
and like what in my parents'
relationship do I admire?
But what I don't--
- Yeah.
- That I need to change,
and they don't communicate.
And today, that's why I think
why it was so important to me
to keep digging and digging
for you to open up,
because I don't want to be
in a relationship
ten years from now
and be able to communicate
with my husband.
- I'll be honest, like,
there's--I've failed a lot
in life.
I failed
at my last relationship.
I'm not gonna lie,
but I needed to fail.
I'm thankful for my fails,
'cause I'm here with you today
because of them.
And no one else I wanna be
with more, you know?
- I'm really proud of you.
Tyler just, like,
completely cracked open
and showed me
more of his heart
and allowed me into things
that I think
are really hard for him
to talk about,
but he did that with me.
And that shows a lot
about the trajectory
of our relationship
and where he will go for me.
I know that
that was hard for you.
Know that I value
taking that step.
And I wanna know who you are,
where you've been
and where you come from.
And I wanna meet your family.
- Yes.
I can't wait for you to meet
my family.
- [laughing] Well...
so, Tyler...
Will you accept this rose?
- Always, Hannah.
Always.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
Aw, come here.
- Tonight, Tyler gave me more
than I even thought he would.
I felt myself in the moment
wanting to, like,
know the faces to the people
that he was talking about
with such passion and love for.
- To be really honest, like,
I'm falling hard for you.
I feel like I am, you know,
falling in love with you.
And I have no doubt in my mind
that I can be the guy
getting on one knee
one day for you.
Yeah, I feel great.
To have this rose
means the world, you know?
I told you, you know, like,
"It feels good
to confide in you,"
and to bring her
to my family...
I'm on top of the world
right now.
- [gasps]
- Aww.
- Babe.
And I am falling in love
for Hannah.
There's an incredible fire
between me and her,
and I just...
it roars, and I can't get
enough of it,
and I just wanna keep
fueling it and fueling it.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thank you for being there
for me tonight.
- You're welcome.
- I'm so excited for next week.
- Me too.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
[doorbell rings]
- Ooh.
- Here it goes.
- Oh, boy.
- Everything we're talking
about, here it comes.
- This week has been tough.
I think we all wanna spend time
with Hannah,
heading into hometowns.
All of us here have had
a one-on-one date.
We know how that time is,
so hoping my name's
on that card.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- "Mike"...
"I'm drawn to you.
Hannah."
- [clapping]
- All righty.
[chuckles]
- So it just means Peter,
Connor, Luke,
group date time, boys.
- Yep.
- Connor, how you feeling, man?
- Honestly, kind of done
with this conversation.
Mike, you know,
congrats to you.
But, like, I'm not--don't
really have anything else
to say right now, so...
♪ ♪
- I feel amazing.
[laughs]
It just continues
to show conviction
that Hannah feels the same way
I feel.
- So, what's going on?
- How you doing?
- If tomorrow goes well,
she may be
the last woman I ever
bring home to my family.
- Even though I do have
strong feelings for her,
I've never really brought
someone home,
and it's hard to see myself
feeling fully comfortable
after another group date.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- You're gonna change
in a different robe.
- All right!
Can I look?
- I'm glad I wore my--
my nice underwear today.
Oh!
[laughing]
- And then...
- I'm fully expecting
a Hail Mary attempt from Luke.
Prepared for battle.
It's a game to Luke.
That's all it is.
- I don't care
what you said to her,
I've been nothing but
truthful with Hannah,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
I'm tired of it, okay?
I'm tired of it!
- [crying]
I don't know what to do,
and I'm scared.
[door opens]
- There he is.
- What's going on?
- Purple suit.
- Purple suit came out.
- Welcome back, man.
- What's up?
- It was good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, it was a great day.
We went horseback riding.
And the nighttime was great.
She was challenging,
she was tough,
and it was really good.
We were able to grow a lot,
so it was a good night.
- Yeah?
- Where's Connor?
- Mike got the one-on-one date,
and Connor was pretty upset
by it.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Yeah, I haven't really seen
much of the guy since then.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
Hey!
- How you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Came to see you.
[both chuckling]
- Well, I'm glad you're here.
- Yeah, it's good to be here.
- Sit on down.
- Oh, yeah.
- What's up?
- Not much, but you're doing
some journaling.
- Doing a little journaling.
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
Why are you here?
Why'd you decide to come?
- So, obviously, like,
this is a big week.
- Uh-huh.
- You know?
Heading into hometowns
and everything,
and, uh...we had
the date card tonight
and my name wasn't on it,
you know,
it's like--it's disappointing.
Um, but yeah, I think
I've said to you for a while,
like, our one-on-one time
has been amazing.
Truly why I wanted
to come up here was spend,
you know, one-on-one time
with you
and kind of just talk
about some stuff.
- I don't know.
One-on-one time has been great.
Obviously,
it's been great together,
but there have been moments
where I've been like
where's Connor, like,
what are you doing, you know?
You've kinda, like,
faded in the group dates.
Do you feel that?
- Yeah, no, definitely felt
I don't always
kind of stick out in the crowd.
But I think I've always
held on to, like,
that one-on-one we had.
- Uh-huh.
- Even though it didn't go
to plan.
It was cut short.
That day,
as crazy as it sounds,
like, I knew I was feeling
those feelings
of falling in love.
And I haven't felt
those feelings
or like a moment like that
in such a long time.
And, you know, I'm excited
to see, you know,
what the future is
and where it goes.
- I give two craps
that Connor didn't get
the one-on-one, but I do feel
for him as an individual,
as a human being.
But we're at the point,
the six of us are great guys,
and it's gonna be upon Hannah
to decide which one
is her great guy.
- It's Hannah's choice,
and just speaks
to what kind of--what she sees
in the future.
- I mean, we're talking
about...we're talking about
a husband for Hannah.
I mean, personally,
I don't see them
having future at all together,
and at this point,
that excites me.
But does Hannah see that?
I don't know.
- You coming here today
is, like,
so great and it's what I want
from you.
But I don't know, like,
going into this week,
it being hometowns.
Like, I wanna feel
very confident in where I am.
You know,
maybe if you came in,
like, weeks ago, you know,
when I was like,
"Where's Connor
in these dates?"
- That's why I did
kind of want
that one-on-one date,
'cause I felt like
if I did have that time,
you know, we would be able
to get there.
- I don't know.
Like, there's nothing bad
about our time together.
Like, it's always good,
but I do feel like
there have been other--there
are other relationships
that...I have...
Stronger feelings with.
And I guess what I'm, like,
looking at,
like, the end of this thing
and, like,
having to make, like,
these really hard decisions...
And...
I don't know if I can see it.
[dramatic musical sting]
- Okay.
I didn't want
this to be good-bye,
and it sucks that it is.
- I'm s-I'm sorry.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[whispers] I'm sorry.
- I definitely
feel heartbroken,
and it hurts.
- Bye.
- [murmurs] See you later.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
It sucks to go do something
that's definitely
out of my comfort zone
and have her tell you,
you know, basically,
it's kinda too little
too late.
We had a powerful connection
early on,
and it's hard to keep
that momentum going
at the same rate
just being on group dates
and the whole time dealing
with Luke's [bleep].
And hearing her say
that she just doesn't feel it
at this point...
it really hurts a lot.
She's an amazing girl,
and I've definitely felt
those feelings
of falling in love and...
It's tough knowing
that that won't happen.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- My date with Jed
set the bar really high
for this week,
because I finally told Jed
I was falling in love with him,
and he has told me.
Hey!
Then yesterday with Tyler,
our relationship exploded,
I feel like, in the best way.
And Tyler told me he was
falling in love with as well.
So today, like,
going in with Mike,
I'm hopeful, you know,
that that could be
a possibility with him
for me too.
Come here.
- You look amazing.
- Oh, thank you.
[laughs]
I was waiting for it.
- [laughs]
Always.
- Hey.
- How're you doing?
- Welcome.
- [laughs]
- So, today, we have
a really fun day in store.
- I'm excited.
- We're going to do like
people in the Netherlands do.
We're gonna go bike.
I'm gonna bike with Mike.
- Bike with Mike, let's do it.
- Let's go.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
I love this.
It's so fun!
Feel like a little kid.
Whoo!
- I'm just really excited,
'cause, you know,
today literally could change
the trajectory
of my entire life.
- Oh, you did it!
- [laughs]
I'm definitely 100%
feeling Hannah,
and I want this so bad.
- It's so pretty.
- The date card said:
"Mike, I'm drawn to you."
- Let's take a loosey
right here.
- I love that.
She's drawn to me
as I'm drawn to her.
What do we have here?
And it's just beautiful,
'cause, you know,
I could be down
on bended knee in a few weeks.
I love art.
- You do?
- What do you think?
Is that a guy or a girl,
you think?
- I think it's a guy.
Look like he's in a shadow.
- What me to tell you
what I saw?
My name is Luta.
- Oh, hello.
- I'm the artist.
- Wow!
- Nice.
- Do you like art?
- I love art.
- I do like art.
- Maybe we can do an afternoon
of painting each other.
- Absolutely.
- Let's do it.
- So, go wild, you know?
Don't be afraid.
Like, go, like, flop!
Fop!
- I feel that love is art.
There's a lot of passion
and a lot of patience.
Let me see it.
And a lot of beauty.
Sometimes you need
to take a step back
to really assess
what's going on.
What?
What is...my cheeks are huge.
She got me looking like
Doe-Doe the Clown or something.
- So, maybe we can switch
it up.
- Yeah!
- See, I did the little
flip-flop.
- Yeah, the flip-flop.
- Hannah is 100% my muse.
For me to capture her beauty,
I mean, that's God's creation.
I can't capture that.
I'ma try.
- Can I look?
I look scared!
Like, I'm like:
[groans]
- We know what we're good at,
and we're gonna stick
to what we're good at.
- Let me try it now.
- Okay.
- You're gonna change
in a different robe.
- All right.
- Man, I did not expect
this date
to go like this at all.
I'm glad I wore
my nice underwear today.
[laughing]
- Oh!
[laughs]
Oh!
You look good.
I like it.
- We always have a fun,
flirty time together,
but she's looking beyond that,
and so am I.
You're looking for their heart
and her soul.
- [hums]
[laughs]
- Her soul looks beautiful.
I never thought we'd be
getting our portrait drawn.
I never thought that.
I did think we would be
this close together, though.
It felt really comfortable
with Hannah in my arms.
I'm so elated and blessed
to be in this position
with Hannah,
the woman that I could be
engaged to here in a few weeks
and the woman that could
be the mother of my children.
My hope is that she feels
the same way about me
as I do for her.
I have some, you know, things
that are on my mind.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know?
A lot of guys are starting
to fall in love with you
and some say they are.
And the way I'm feeling
is that
I take this very seriously.
- Just know that.
- I know, I know that.
And I feel like it's been hard,
obviously, but now it's like,
we're all, like, expressing
our feelings more.
And I am too, and you have to
before you go into a home.
- I agree with you so much.
This morning,
I was just super nervous.
I was like,
"Today may be the first day,"
you know, "with my wife."
- Mike is always very honest
and very open
about how he feels
at all times.
That's all I've been asking
for from everyone here
is just be to honest and real.
But right now, I'm trying to
decipher what I feel.
- Come here.
I need that.
[chuckles]
Hey.
- It's crucial that tonight
I can see a glimpse
of the future with Mike.
If I give Mike a rose
and we go to hometowns
and I go home,
I'm going to look his mom,
his grandmother, and his sister
in the eyes.
They're gonna ask how I feel
about him,
and I need to be confident
in what I say.
And right now,
I don't know what I would say.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic string music
continues]
♪ ♪
- Being with Hannah,
we had a wonderful
day portion of our date.
And the way Hannah makes me
feel is I want more.
I want more and I want more
and I want more.
Every time
we leave each other,
I think that we both want
more of each other.
- [sniffs]
- Tonight it's gonna be
extremely clear that I want
Hannah to be my wife.
For me to get a rose tonight
and Hannah decides
to go to my hometown
and she meets my mother,
my grandmother,
and my sister--
literally I feel 100%.
The other guys might
as well go home.
[laughs]
- How are you?
- Better.
You look amazing.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Sorry, my hands
are really sweaty.
I've been having a hard night.
So let's just go sit down
and talk.
- Okay.
- Is that okay?
- [sniffles]
[sighs]
- This is beautiful.
- Yeah, it's amazing.
[sniffs]
Thank you.
- Hey, we kinda match.
- Oh, you look really nice.
- No, you look better.
- No, like, wow.
You look really good.
- We complement each other.
- I've been here
for a little while.
And...
Like, I got to, like,
see all the, like,
art and stuff and...
- Yeah.
- I've never been
surrounded by, like,
so much...
Beauty and...
- You deserve it.
- It's just like
really overwhelming.
[sniffs]
There was this painting.
It was, like, Saint Catherine
and she, like,
is holding a sword
and a Bible
and there's like these men
in the background
and they're, like, all
fighting and it just, like--
it really just
encompassed everything
that I'm going through
right now I think.
[sniffles]
And what I feel like and...
[exhales]
- Take your time.
- This is just, like,
this is my life and...
- Exactly.
- I can't control when things
are gonna hit me
and when things are going--
- Such is life.
- Yeah.
- Can I just give you a hug?
- Let me just give you a hug.
[both laughing]
- I needed a hug.
- [chuckling]
- Um...
- Are you okay?
[dramatic music]
- No, I'm not okay.
♪ ♪
- What's on your mind?
Say it.
- I think I've just been, like,
thinking a lot
since I've been here and, like,
you've been, like,
such a leader here.
And I told you like
the first t--like,
in the Rose Ceremony the first
day I was so freaking nervous
and all I could see, like,
you were just smiling
and you, like,
got me through it.
You know?
[sniffs]
And, um, I know one
of the first conversations
we had was, like...
[sniffs]
How you don't wanna, like,
get your heart broken.
And I know how bad that hurts.
[sniffs]
And you've talked about your
three ladies in your life.
They're so amazing and, like,
you're looking
for your fourth lady,
and I know that I'm not
that fourth lady.
[exhales]
- I know it's hard to say,
But it's what's needed to say,
of how you feel.
- [sniffles]
- I can't say that I'm happy.
- [whispers] Sorry.
- I don't know what to say
except...
thank you for being honest.
- [sighs]
[crying]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Thank you, Mike.
[crying]
Okay.
♪ ♪
[groans]
I'm really proud of you
and who you are
and the man that you are.
[sniffs]
This is by far the hardest
good-bye that I've had to say,
and it's because of how good
of a human Mike is.
Mike deserves to be loved
fiercely just as much as I do.
♪ ♪
[crying]
And it hurts to hurt people
along the way
for something
that you believe in.
♪ ♪
I just feel bad.
[crying]
Trying to be strong,
trying to keep my faith,
and I'm trying to rely
on the thing
that's far greater than me.
But I don't know what to do,
and I'm scared.
♪ ♪
- It's like...her putting
a dagger in my heart
and tearing it out
and then stepping on it.
♪ ♪
I know that I'm ready for love
and I know that I was opening
my heart up to Hannah,
and I know that...
She crushed me.
♪ ♪
- At this point,
to see someone come in
and take his suitcase,
that'd make my day.
- Oh, we know.
We know.
- I mean,
you guys are in my way.
- [chuckling]
- Just being completely real.
Is something funny over there,
Tyler?
- Yeah.
The worst thing about all this
is, like, we have a villain.
And usually the villain's like
some big, you know,
tall--we got a 5'8" villain.
- Does that make
you feel better?
- So, yeah, I just wanna
throw that out there.
- To me right now,
the only person that--
if anyone feels uncomfortable,
it's when I'm in the room
with you.
- When we were in Scotland and
there's 15 guys in the house
and 14 guys don't like you,
like, maybe it's not, you know,
we're the problem.
Maybe it's, "I'm the problem."
- It's not like 14 guys
didn't like me.
- You're right--now there's
five guys that can't stand you.
And--
- Really?
I was just in the room hanging
out with all these guys--
'cause it's you.
Me and Garrett were
just shooting--
- 'Cause we have
to put up with you.
- Luke, the cutting up that
we had was [bleep] on my part.
- Okay, cool.
- 'Cause I'm not the type
of person to just ignore you.
- And let me--let me
ask you something.
- So I was giving you
a [bleep] response, dude.
- Sorry, I'm not trying
to completely disrespect you.
- Well, you definitely
interrupted me, too,
so it's okay.
- I want--
I want to ask you a question.
- Go for it.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Well, I hope you're happy,
man.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, I'm happy
his suitcase is gone.
- A good dude that just left?
- That's your
[bleep] show, dude.
- He's gone,
so guess what.
One less--less of us.
Simple math.
There's three guys
on this group date.
One rose.
Mike's suitcase gets taken away
and now there's two roses
and I'm the only one
that's happy?
- Listen, are we gonna have
any issues tomorrow?
- No, I'm--I'm totally cool.
- I swear, man, you pull
[bleep] tomorrow, oh, man.
I'm just saying,
Pete and I are prepared for it.
I'm fully expecting a
Hail Mary attempt from Luke.
The fact is the guy's selfish.
Luke has thrown people
under the bus before.
And the moment
he does that to me,
I'm gonna do something
about it.
Prepared for a battle.
- Garrett, Peter,
we're praying for you guys.
We're praying for Hannah.
Wish you all the best.
- And Luke, man, just keep your
head out of your ass, man.
Just don't worry about
the other guys.
- Out of all people,
I'm surprised you had the balls
to tell me that,
but I'll keep that in mind.
- Yeah.
- All right, fellas,
well, go have a date.
- Let's do it, let's go.
- All right, boys.
- Now we're at
the final group date.
And the fact is today
the good guys are gonna win.
You know, I fully anticipate
Peter and I coming out
with roses here.
And the bad guy's going home.
It's about time.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
It's a game to Luke.
That's--that's all it is.
[tense music]
He loves the idea of winning
"The Bachelorette."
He doesn't love the idea
of falling in love with Hannah.
- Hey, hey.
- Hey.
- Oh, goodness.
- Hello, beautiful.
- [laughs]
- How are you?
- Hi.
- So good to see you.
- It's good to see you.
- I love this color on you.
- Hey, thank you.
- You look
absolutely beautiful.
- Hey.
Oh, thank you.
- You feeling better?
- I am.
I--I can actually talk.
- Sound way better.
- Yeah.
Um, today's gonna be hard.
And I know that,
but let's just try to make it
as fun as possible.
- All right, let's do it.
- So...
[laughs]
- All righty.
- Last night was really
difficult for me.
I got really emotional
sending Mike home.
And so I don't wanna bring
that into the date today.
- This place is incredible.
[mellow music]
Hometowns are next week,
and so I feel the weight of it.
It's really important that
I really do have developing
feelings for these guys--
feelings of love.
- Oh, looky here.
- Oh, ho, ho!
- I definitely think the heart
wants what the heart wants
and I know that my heart's
in a good place.
So I hope my mind can be
comfortable with what
my heart wants.
all: Cheers.
[glass clinking]
- Cheers]
Hannah, can--
- Yeah.
- Can I steal you?
Let's go for a walk.
[receding footsteps]
How are you?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- So you wanna just take
the two roses and run?
- Should we? Let's just
get out of here, dude.
Go steal Hannah and, uh,
head back to the hotel.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Good now that I have you alone.
- How's this week been?
- It's been--I just--I--I--
you know me.
I hate talking about
the other guys.
But, you know, I don't have
to say any names because...
a lot of the time I wish
you were a fly on the wall
and you could see their
character be exposed.
And, like, I've done nothing.
I've apologized to you many--
- You don't feel like
you've done anything?
- The last thing that was said
to me before I walked out
of the house,
Jed looks at me and he's like,
"Yeah, I got advice for you,
Luke.
Uh, try and keep your head
out of your ass."
Out of all people, like,
I expect that from Tyler.
I've been getting comments
like that from him
and other people.
But to hear that from Jed,
that concerns me for you.
And, like, the character
that they've shown me.
Like, last night Garrett,
he, like, starts calling me out
and I go, like,
"Why are you--why are you
"acting so different?
You and I were just
cutting it up yesterday."
And he goes,
"Yeah, sorry about that.
That was me being fake.
I shouldn't have been
doing that with you."
Huh?
Like, to me, that sh--
like shocks
the hell out of me.
For you.
- I just, like, don't...
like, get why people
won't be kind to you.
Like, what is it?
Like, I'm sorry,
I just need to know.
- Do you remember being
on this side?
- Yeah.
- It's like you're a part
of a mob.
If I screw up time and I rob
them time with you, guess what.
They all turn on me,
hate me,
and start saying some crap
that's totally fake
and not true about me,
and it's the thing I've been
dealing with this whole time.
And that's the only reason
why they dislike me.
That's the truth.
♪ ♪
- It's so frustrating because
I know we see, you know,
one side of it
when he's not with her.
- It sucks.
The guy's--the guy's a [bleep].
- It's just like
it disgusts me how fake he is
and it's like I get why Hannah
probably doesn't see it.
You know?
'Cause he does such a good job
of manipulating.
- But I just want you to know
through it all
I've gotten to see sides
of you that I know
they haven't seen yet.
Because we've had to deal with
all this crap, so to speak.
And honestly it's, like--it's--
it's done nothing
but affirm me
how I feel about you
and it's made it grow
so strong.
Seriously, Hannah.
And I know it's--you're
probably gonna look at me
and say,
"You don't even know me."
[laughs]
I like to think I do.
♪ ♪
- I am exhausted from
the drama with Luke.
Has it been some
of his own fault?
Yeah.
I'm smart and I see issues.
But then I'm like,
am I missing something
so much more,
or is it just boys being boys?
So I'm just trying to figure
out what I believe is true.
How you doing?
- I gotta be real with you.
- Yeah?
- I haven't been sleeping much.
- Why?
- 'Cause we had such a great
time on our one-on-one.
- Mm-hmm.
- And as nervous as I was to
admit to you that I was falling
in love with you,
I woke up the next morning
feeling at peace about it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And that's exactly
the way I feel.
Exactly.
But it was a tough week.
You know? It was--
- I know.
- I'm just happy
to be here right now.
Happy to be here with you.
- Yeah.
Well, I'm glad
that you're here.
This week's been hard on me,
too.
Like...
Um, I just talked
to Luke and...
I don't know.
Like, he was just
talking about, like,
just some things that
happened last night,
and what really bothered me
is were y'all, like,
being cordial with each other
and then, like--
then you were ragging
on him later on?
Did you say that you were
being fake nice to him?
- I didn't say fake nice.
I said I was responding to him.
But I--I told him I was
[bleep] because
I can't sit there,
if someone's talking to me,
I'm not gonna say, "Shut up."
I'm not gonna ignore him.
I'm gonna respond
back to him.
And I responded back to him
very quickly.
- Like, when I don't
like somebody,
I just don't like them.
And they know
I don't like them.
I don't want somebody to ever,
like, try to be fake.
- I get that.
You're stronger than me
for being able to tell someone
to their face
that you don't like them,
and to me by responding short
is my version of,
"I don't like you."
And I did say that because
I was very, very frustrated
in the moment.
I've got things that I really
want to tell you.
Good things.
And it's the Luke P.
show right now still.
And it's not fair
for our relationship.
It's not fair for anyone's
relationship with you.
And we're all at a point where
we're just frustrated with it.
- Okay.
I'm sorry that this is, like,
what I needed to talk about.
- Don't--no.
- It's a--it's a hard decision
for me to make
at this point and like--
- I get it--I'm not upset at
you at all that you're asking.
- Mm-hmm.
- Please understand that.
Hail Mary, right?
I called it.
I'm frustrated that my time
with Hannah in this great city
has gone to talking
about Luke.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
He doesn't have much on me,
so the fact that
he pulled something
from a conversation
from last night with the group
shows that he's willing to try
anything at this point.
Even if he tries to dig
this hole and push me in it
right now,
I'm gonna climb back out.
- What's happening?
- You tell me, man.
I know for a fact right now
I will not go home
because of Luke P.
I saw the look on her face,
and your time's coming
to an end.
- Excuse me?
[dramatic musical sting]
- Hannah tells me that you
talked to her about me.
[tense music]
Again.
Didn't you say last night that
you weren't gonna throw
any Hail Marys and you were
gonna stay in your own lane?
- Well, if Hannah
asks me something,
I'm gonna answer it.
- Exactly, which is why
I answered her question
when she asked me about you.
But I didn't bring you up.
- Good.
- She brought you up.
And I answered it.
- Good.
Yeah, it is good.
- All right, great.
- It's very good, man.
♪ ♪
It's very, very good.
- I got nothing to say
to you right now.
- That's okay.
'Cause I know it's just gonna
be [bleep] anyway
like it always has been.
But something tells me
Hannah's gonna know it, too.
- Hannah's gonna know what?
- That everything you say
is [bleep].
- I've been giving Hannah
nothing but the truth
this whole time.
- Okay.
In your eyes, everyone else
has the issue
and everyone else puts you
in these situations,
but are we starting to think
that maybe it's Luke's fault?
- Okay.
- It's your fault.
You talk about everybody.
You're the fakest person
I've ever met.
- You don't even know me.
- Oh, I know you,
and I'll double point
on that one.
Double pistols.
I know you whether you
like it or not,
and I don't give a [bleep]
either way.
Everybody knows you.
- I'm tired of seeing this
fake smirk on your face.
- It's a real smirk, my friend.
- This is the fakest smile
I've ever seen.
- It's a real smile.
Look at it, baby.
This is real.
- I'm tired of this, okay?
I'm done.
- Well, I'm gonna keep going,
so until you do
something about it,
I'm just gonna keep going.
- Do something about what?
- I'm gonna keep--
- If Hannah asks me a question,
I'm gonna answer it.
How many times do I have
to tell you that?
- So she asked you,
"Why did Garrett say
he was [bleep]
you last night,"
when she wasn't even there
in that conversation?
- She asked me what I thought
about you.
And she asked me
what's been go--
- Oh, so the truth comes out.
Okay.
- Yeah.
She asked me how--
- Ah.
- What's been going on lately.
- You are a weasel.
- I'm a weasel?
- Weasel or a snake
is the best way to put it.
- A snake?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Really?
- Luke psychopath the snake,
man.
Yeah.
- Your words are meaningless.
- Well, you know what?
Hannah seemed to appreciate
what I had to say.
So that's all I care about.
I don't care what you think,
dude.
- You disgust me.
- That's fantastic.
- You make me want to gag.
- Luke, Luke, Luke, man.
You might not see it,
but you're falling.
And you're reaching
for branches.
- I am never--
and I'm not ever--
going to reach for anything.
I've been nothing but truthful
with Hannah.
And you are not
gonna mess it up, okay?
- I'm not gonna mess it up?
- No!
I don't care what
you said to her,
but I am tired of it.
You know what this
is right here?
This is a pile of bologna.
Look at that.
♪ ♪
That's what you've
been saying to me,
and I'm tired of it, okay?
- I'll put this back.
- I'm tired of it, okay?
- Okay.
Be tired of it, man.
Be tired of it.
- Be real with that woman!
She's looking for a husband!
- Be real with her?
- Be real with her, okay?
I'm not gonna let you screw
this up for me.
- It's funny
you picked up bologna,
because that's exactly
what you are, man.
♪ ♪
As we all saw now
two weeks in a row,
when he's faced with something
that's confronting him,
the guy explodes.
Luke has reached a new level
of childish behavior
that he pulls bologna out
of his little lunch box.
- What's up, man?
- What's up?
- You talk to Hannah yet?
- No, not yet.
How'd your talk go with--
[sirens blaring]
- Honestly it didn't go any way
I had planned.
I had no intention
of talking about anyone.
And what do you know?
I had to talk about how things
have been in the hotel
and stuff because
Hannah asked me.
And I just want you to know
that that went on because,
you know, I just had Garrett
over here come up to me
and just feed me a bunch
of bologna.
And it's--
- Dude, bologna?
Like, we literally
talked about this.
Like, you like essentially
gave me your word, like,
last night you would stay
in your lane.
Like, you were only focusing
on your relationship
with Hannah.
This is not how I wanted
to spend my possible last date
ever with her.
- Do you think--
you think I wanted
to spend it like this?
- It just, like, doesn't end.
Like--
So she's not--not
in a good headspace now?
Is that what you're
trying to say?
Dude, I haven't even talked
to her yet today.
Like, all right, listen,
I'm--
I'm done with this.
I'm so sick of this guy.
There's always a chance that
this is my last date with her.
But I will be there
100% for her.
You know, if she needs to lean
on me or whatnot,
like, I've got her, you know?
That's my girl.
And there's no way in hell
that Luke tries
to tear her down today.
So you doing good, though?
- Mm-hmm.
- With this whole thing?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Yeah?
- I'm better now.
- Awesome.
- How are you?
- This is, um...
Yeah, we haven't really talked
I guess since our one-on-one.
This is, like, the first time.
- Mmm.
- I had so much clarity
after that night
of just my feelings for you.
And it's scary.
It really is scary.
- I know.
- But obviously like for me
family is everything.
- Yeah.
- And the thought of, like,
introducing you to my family
is--oh, my God.
Like, my heart right now is,
like, just filled
with happiness just
thinking about that.
How are you feeling about
possibly coming there?
- Um, I mean, I feel like
if I'm not nervous
then I'm not taking
it seriously.
But ultimately, like,
I don't know.
I'm excited.
- You are?
- I'm excited.
- Good.
Hannah, there's so many things
that I admire about you
and it's, like,
why I'm falling for you.
Like, it's--it's so--it's dumb.
Like I--I'm like--
- You're making me blush
so much right now.
- No, I'm--I'm smitten by you,
obviously.
Like, I love how goofy you are
and how strong you are
and, you know,
raw and it's sexy.
Like, and I--you're just
so honest and, like,
I truly, like, have never met
someone like you before.
And, like, I'm loving this.
And I don't want it to end.
And I just feel like I can't
tell you this stuff enough
'cause it's coming straight
from the heart here, and--
- I feel it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Good.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- I'm feeling great
about Peter.
I'm really excited about
our relationship.
I feel like it's continually
moving forward
and I do see
a future with him.
- I'm crazy about you.
♪ ♪
- He is just a nice
break always
from the mess
and the drama.
♪ ♪
I want to give this rose
to someone who always
just makes me feel special,
important,
and the distractions
don't matter.
So Peter.
- [chuckles]
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- I would love to.
I can't wait.
♪ ♪
I'm so excited.
- Me, too.
- Seriously, like--
- No--
both: Whoo!
[laughs]
- Come here.
I am falling so,
so hard for this girl.
And I'm going to hometowns,
you know?
She's gonna meet my family.
She's meeting Webers.
And I love the sound
of Hannah Weber.
[bells tolling]
- [laughs]
- Yes.
Like, this is happening.
- Bye.
- Whoo!
- [laughs]
Whoo!
- Bye, beautiful.
- Bye.
both: See you soon.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Are you licking your lips
because you're attracted to me?
♪ ♪
I wish it was me that got
the Group Date Rose,
but I'm not surprised
that Peter got it.
You know, coming into this,
I had a feeling that
Luke was gonna come
after me anyway.
So now it's down
to the nitty-gritty
and even though today didn't
go as planned,
I really don't feel nervous
about tonight.
Luke's digging his own grave.
It's gonna be me and Peter
at the end of the night.
I know that.
That's why I'm smiling.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Tonight's a huge night for
Hannah and I's relationship.
What I wanna do is I wanna
show her that, yeah,
I got thrown under the bus
earlier today
but it doesn't mean
I'm gonna dwell on it,
and from here on out Hannah
and I can focus on us.
This rose tonight means
that Hannah can see
a future with me.
It means that Hannah
wants to meet my family.
And it means everything.
♪ ♪
- Garrett.
You look nice, man.
- Thanks.
As far as I'm concerned,
Luke's not there.
It's just myself and Hannah.
Hello, Hannah.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
How are you?
- Doing wonderful.
- Thank you.
- You look great.
- I'm diggin' the dress.
- Thank you.
Oh.
Today was hard.
Tonight is going to be harder.
Um, I have strong relationships
with both of you,
and honestly I don't want
to bring any drama
or negativity into tonight.
I just want to focus on really
making sure I'm confident
in who I'm going
to go home with
and meet a family.
And, um, so, um,
here's to exploring
our relationships
and the potential of a future.
So, cheers.
- Cheers.
- Cheers to that.
[glasses clinking]
- I know that today,
things didn't go
as good as I had
thought they would.
So this night is much
needed for me.
♪ ♪
I really want her to see
the real me.
I think this is a perfect time
to open up about things
in my past and I definitely
know it's gonna open
Hannah's eyes to get
to know me better.
You know, growing up as a kid,
you know,
sports was a huge part
of my life.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, I wasn't like
a wild child, like,
bad punk kid or anything.
I was the same me.
I was just, you know,
I was exploring things.
I was experimenting and, like,
with drinking and partying
and stuff,
and then, you know,
freshman year, like,
I chased drinking excessively.
Uh, I did some stupid things.
Like, there was a--a streak
of me where I was chasing sex.
Like, it--it just...
This is hard for me
to talk about.
- It's okay.
- Um...
- I just want you--I want
to know everything, so...
- Yeah.
It's not easy for me
to talk about 'cause I--
I hated, like, chasing those
selfish, like,
fleshly desires, right?
- Mmm.
- And all this unfulfillment.
Like, nothing satisfied me.
And it started hitting me.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then here's where
the story gets good.
I'm getting in the shower
and I just remember
feeling this heavy
weight on me.
And I just remember bawling
my eyes out.
I remember feeling a voice
telling me,
"Luke, let go."
I remember, like,
looking at the ceiling
and I remember I could, like,
see a glimpse of, like, Heaven.
And I remember thinking
to myself,
"This is what I need
to look forward to."
And since then I've been
completely on fire.
And, no, it wasn't, like,
overnight I'm just
this perfect person.
You know that this walk--
- I was gonna say, yeah.
- Yeah.
You know this walk isn't easy.
- It's hard and since then I've
been doing everything I--
I can to become what I feel
like my future dream wife
is looking for in a husband.
- Thank you.
I know that's hard...
- Yeah.
- First of all.
Your past is your past.
And if you didn't go
through all that...
- Mmm.
- Then you don't, like,
see the blessings, really.
I feel like my experience
is similar in a way.
I appreciate things
so much more
and, like, what the Lord, like,
did in my life.
It was really cool to hear him
share his testimony.
I like that he is open
about his faith and...
I'm connected to him.
- I'm loving this.
I wish we had more of this.
But you know what?
- Do you wanna kiss me?
- Yes.
[both laughing]
♪ ♪
I couldn't feel better
right now.
I know that I can--I can be
ready soon
to get down
on one knee, 100%.
I genuinely feel that way
without a shadow of a doubt.
And I'll be confident to say
that she's falling in love
with me for sure.
I mean, how could I not
be more confident?
[laughs]
It's like I know.
- I think Hannah doesn't see
the same Luke we see
and is being manipulated
by Luke and blinded by
whatever façade
he's putting on.
- Yeah.
[all shouting]
[all laughing]
- I genuinely want the world
for Hannah.
And to see Peter walk
through that door,
that means another great
gentleman is back.
You know, hopefully today's
the end of the Luke P. show
and we can get this dude
in our rearview mirror.
- It was awkward as hell.
Luke was just sitting there
and just had this look
in his face and, like,
the guy's--
he's totally imploding, so--
- Oh, yeah.
- I got all the confidence
in the world that
Garrett's coming back tonight.
- Garrett's gonna
crush him tonight.
- Yeah.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
You look fantastic.
- Thank you.
- We got hometowns right
around the corner.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I already know I'm very
comfortable with you
meeting my family.
I'm sure it's written all over
my dang face right now.
But it's just--it speaks
to who you are,
it speaks to what you're about,
and it speaks to how
I feel about you.
- Oh!
- I told you ever since
I first met you that
you push me
and you help me grow.
And I struggled with
being confident.
I struggled with being open.
- I'm just so excited of, like,
the growth that has been
made here.
It's been--
- It's you.
This ain't me.
This is your doing.
I appreciate it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You make me feel some type
of way, Hannah Brown.
Some type of way.
And, oh, God,
I just can't wait for you
to meet the family.
- [laughs]
- I ca--I just can't wait.
It's--
It was difficult for me
to tell you that I was falling
in love with you--it was.
But the fact is, man, it hit
me like a ton of bricks today.
It's...
I love you.
♪ ♪
There was just something in me
that knew I had to say it.
♪ ♪
I'm buzzing, like,
just so hard right now
off of nothing but that moment.
I used to wait, like,
years before I thought
I was comfortable to say
something like that.
But then the L-bomb came out,
and it's just--
this night has exceeded
the expectations
that I deep down had for it.
And it was exactly what
I was looking for,
and I'm sure it was exactly
what Hannah was looking for.
I'm not even gonna try
to be modest about it.
This rose is coming
back with me,
big time.
And...
Hannah and I will be
in Birmingham soon.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Tonight is a really
difficult decision for me.
Two great guys and two really
strong relationships
that I've had.
I feel like my relationship
with Garrett
is definitely growing.
Garrett told me
that he loves me
and that is so wild because
he's the first person here
that has said
I love you to me.
He's the first person
in a long time
that said I love you to me.
My conversation with Luke
went really well.
Of course we talked
about our faith,
but I didn't know exactly
how his faith
came into play in his life.
Although Luke and I's
relationship is complicated,
we have a very
intense connection.
I have fears about
this decision.
But I'm going where I feel
like my heart is leading me.
Thank you.
- [groans]
It's inevitable that there's
only one rose,
and having
two great conversations
doesn't make it
any easier for me.
I'm sorry.
Um, this is just really hard.
[dramatic music]
You're both wonderful.
But I have to give this rose
to someone who
not only opened up
their heart
but showed me
inside their heart.
And I have to go with my gut
and what my heart
is drawing me to.
♪ ♪
Luke, will you accept
this rose?
- Most definitely.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't apologize.
Gave it all I got.
- I know that.
- Thanks for hanging
in there with me.
Thanks for everything.
♪ ♪
I won't forget you.
- I won't forget you.
♪ ♪
- Don't hide that red nose,
all right?
- [laughs]
I won't.
- [softly] Good.
Bye, Hannah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffing]
- I'm just so rocked
right now.
I'm still in love with Hannah.
[intense music]
The fact is I--I'm just
so shell-shocked.
♪ ♪
It's gonna be hard to put
myself out there
again like that.
I've never put it
out there like that.
[heavy, dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Shocker.
Every freaking time.
♪ ♪
- There's a real opportunity
that she's going to end up
with Luke.
The guy schemed his way
into hometowns.
He's done it every single week.
♪ ♪
I'm so [bleep] pissed off.
Luke's gonna keep saying
what Hannah wants to hear.
It's gonna last for the rest
of her life.
♪ ♪
And she has no idea.
[Hannah murmuring,
Luke laughing]
- Every time
you think he's gone,
he's not.
♪ ♪
- Yes!
We're going to Georgia.
[laughs]
- Coming up,
when the dramatic season
of "The Bachelorette"
continues...
- Luke really lives his faith.
We're on a good path.
- Somehow her heart
is softened to you.
And you know what?
That is a gift, like,
we could never deserve.
- This house right here is
the house that I grew up in.
- That means a lot
that you want me here.
- I look at you with her like,
"Oh, my gosh.
He might be in love."
- I am in love
with Hannah Brown.
And I can't wait to tell her.
- Whoo!
I'm loving this.
- There's no more secret.
It's out.
I am in love with Hannah.
- I'm, like, so attracted
to you in every way.
I love everything about you.
- Things have heated up,
that's for sure.
I need to cool myself down.
- I don't want
to just have sex.
I want to connect
on a deeper level.
- This is what I want.
- Yeah.
- For the rest of my life.
There is definitely sexual
tension between us.
But I know Hannah
and I know that having sex
in the fantasy suite
is something
that's not gonna happen.
[thunder clapping]
So let's talk about sex.
- Okay.
- And let's say you have
had sex
with one
or multiple of these guys.
I'd completely remove myself
from this relationship.
- How dare I be judged
by a man.
My husband would never say
what you've said to me.
I have had sex.
- [groaning]
- And honestly,
Jesus still loves me.
[dramatic music]
From--from obviously
how you feel,
me [bleep] in a windmill,
probably--you probably
want to leave.
- Say what?
- Yeah.
I [bleep] in a windmill.
And guess what.
We did it a second time.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[music lightens up]
[knuckles cracking]
♪ ♪
[light, teasing music
continues]
♪ ♪